Division of Invertebrate Paleontology Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Photographs, Series III
  - People., 001283
    - Photographs & Negatives. Invertebrate Paleontology Portrait Gallery; Photographs, prints and negatives of the following individuals, people:, 000702
    - Photographs. Photograph - Sam Ciurca working at Passage Gulf, 1966, 000889
  - Slides., 001284
    - Photographs & Negatives. Slides received from the YPM Div. of Entomology with the amber collection. Includes a slide of YPM IP 1001 - Dunbaria fasciipennis, YPM IP 322743 - undet. Chilopoda, 002726
    - Slides. A partial set of 35 mm slides of the artwork in the Invertebrate Hall including the following taxonomic groups: vertebrates, plants, protists, sponges, hydrozoans, scyphozoans, brachiopods, echinoderms, plants and vertebrates 35 mm slides. 1950's, 000545
    - Slides. 35 mm color slides of Peter Robinson's "Pipe Line" locality in Tres Hermanos, New Mexico. 35 mm slides, 1960; 000572
    - Slides. 35mm color slides of Duane Mellor, Cretaceous localities from Wyoming 35mm color slides. 1975-76, 000579
    - Slides. 35 mm coler slides of dissertation area of Susan Kidwell; Maryland & Virgina 35 mm coler slides, 1981; 000675
    - Slides. 35 mm slides of Beecher's Trilobite Bed material returned from Tubingen University by John E. Almond, return of loan of Beecher trilobites received February 12, 1992. These slides document the poor condition in which the specimens were received. 35 mm color slides., 000540
    - Slides. Master set of 35 mm slides of invertebrate fossils from the Yale Peabody Museum, Division of Invertebrate Paleontology. Photography by W.K. Sacco and K. Carlson. Includes slides of specimens as well as slides of the portraits of Karl Waage, Carl Dunbar, Charles Schuchert, and Charles Beecher., 000670
    - Slides. Loaner set of 35 mm slides of invertebrate fossils from the Yale Peabody Museum, Division of Invertebrate Paleontology. Photography by W.K. Sacco, J.R. Barbour, K. Carlson, B.S. Lieberman, R.D. White and A.H. Rehn., 000673
    - Slides. Slides of localities - Galloway-St. Jean Stromatoporoid Collection, 000895
    - Slides. Conservation record of Redfield Wall Chart - before and after slides taken by conservator, extra bits of paper from the chart, 000925
    - X-ray file. One drawer of unpublished radiographs (X-rays) of "Beecher bed" fossils from Ordovician Frankfort Sh near Rome New York; "square" number stikers on specimens and on radiographs are Sturmer's private numbers; see W. Sturmer letters., 1984; 000919
  - Specimens. Photographs & Negatives., 001281
    - Drawing. unpublished figures for 1879 "Description of new species of fossils from the Calciferous Formation" IP Reprint # 6347, 1885; 000888
    - Drawing. original ontogenetic drawings of brachiopod Richthofenia by Robert T. Jackson & response letter by C. Schuchert. 1920+/-, 000697
    - Drawing. drawings of Fox Hills Fm Scaphitidae., 1974; 000530
    - Drawing. Suture drawings & black & white negatives & prints of scaphitid ammonoids (Discoscaphites conradi, D. gulosus), Prairie Bluff; see repr. 372, Jeletzky & Waage, 1978 Black & white negatives & photos, 000681
    - Locality information. Locality information and specimen photos, Kinzers Formation Camptostroma, 000931
    - Manuscript material. Duplicate set of photographs for eurypterid paper received from Kjellesvig-Waering on January 12, 1969., 003141
    - Manuscript material. Photographs of Maryland Eurypterus flintstonensis, taken by Ciurca, 1970., 003143
    - Negatives. Black and white glass negative of Fusulina. M. E. Upson, Accn. IPA.07545, 002428
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white glass negatives of insect wings; includes Pennsylvanian Mazon Creek cockroaches, 1902; 000631
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints of Lower Devonian Helderbergian crinoid slab, which is mounted on the second floor of the Peabody Museum, plus slab located in the basement of the Museum. Black and white prints, 1905; 000595
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints of Palaeosoic Arachnoida; original plates; Pennsylvanian Mazon Creek, 1913; 000640
    - Photographs & Negatives. Longwell; black and white glass negatives of Pennsylvanian fusulines from Nevada ;Waage; black & white negatives, color lantern slides & 2"x2" slides, of ammonites, concs. & maps & charts; Fox Hills Fm, South Dakota;Ziegler; color slides of continental plate drift movements Black and white glass negatives; color slides. ca 1920; 1980, 000613
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints and glass negatives of Silurian brachiopods Black and white prints and glass negatives, 1928; 000616
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white glass negatives of Silurian trilobites from Arkansas Black and white glass negatives. ca 1929, 000619
    - Photographs & Negatives. Glass black and white negatives of Pleistocene molluscs from New Milford, CT. Black and white glass negatives, 1930; 000614
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints and glass negatives of Ordovician brachiopods, trilobites, etc. form Perce, Quebec. Black and white prints & glass negatives, 1930; 000617
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints of fusulinids from Haymond, Texas black and white prints. 1931-1932, 000576
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints of fusulinids from Shasta Co., California Black and white prints, 1932; 000578
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints of fusulinids from West Texas prints. ca 1934, 000574
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints of Ordovician Nautiloids from Newfoundland Black and white prints. ca 1935, 000584
    - Photographs & Negatives. Measurements, drawings, plates, diagrams, & black & white negatives & prints for unpublished Masters thesis on Lophophyllidium & Tortiphyllum corals, 1938; 000666
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints of fusulines from limestone of the Ingleside Fm near Owl Creek Canyon, 15 mi NW of Fort Collins, Larimer Co, North Central Colorado Black and white prints, 1939; 000569
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white negatives from Yang's dissertation, Traverse Grp, Michigan, 1939; 000642
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white negatives, glass and other, from Yang's unfinished dissertation; Traverse Grp, Michigan, 1939; 000644
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white negatives of Pennsylvanian fsulinids from Kansas and Nebraska black and white negatives. ca 1940, 000589
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints and negatives of brachiopods and bivalves from Yang's dissertation. photographed 1941. Black and white prints and negatives, 000604
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints of fusulines from the Wells formation and the Morgan formation of Utah. Black and white print., 1943; 000570
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints and negatives of fusulinids from Permian Pakelenica Dol. from Velebit, Yugoslavia negatives; black and white prints, 1951; 000577
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints and negatives of fusulines from Telegraph Creek, British Columbia, Canada. Black and white print., 1953; 000571
    - Photographs & Negatives. 4x5 negatives and prints for Buehler (1955) Bulletin on Halysitidae., 000699
    - Photographs & Negatives. 8x10 black white print of a radiograph of YPM 228, Triarthrus eatoni. black and white print. ca 1970, 000549
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and White prints of Bretsky (1970) plates including brachipopods, bivalves and gastropods; dissertation., 000629
    - Photographs & Negatives. Nineteen black and white, 2x4 prints of edrioasteroids including: YPM 24803a, Lepidodiscus squamosus; YPM 24803b, Lepidodiscus squamosus; YPM 28451 Lebetodiscus dicksoni; YPM 28452 Foerstediscus grandis; YPM 28453, Cystaster stellatus; YPM 28455, Edrioast. ca 1976er priscus. Black and white prints, 000560
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white negatives of Proterea clemvillensis Parks from Quebec black and white negatives, 1981; 000596
    - Photographs & Negatives. Two 3x4 color transparencies of YPM 2424, Placenticeras whitfieldi and YPM 2425, a slab of Jurassic ammonites from Lyme Regis, England. Color transparencies, 1983; 000564
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and White prints of Ordovician nautiloids from Newfoundland. Recovered by RDW & CM at New Mexico Bureau of Mines, Minerals and Resources Black and white prints, 1984; 000583
    - Photographs & Negatives. A series of 2x3 black and white prints for U. Rehfeld's dissertation (Heidelberg University) including YPM Nos. 9895, 2096, 2025, 2095, 2019, 2100, 1025, 2022, 2021, 2098,2023, 2024, 6884, 867, 1015, 2097, 1024, 94, 1018, 1017, 1016, 1020, Black and white print. ca 1985, 000562
    - Photographs & Negatives. One 3x4 black and white print of YPM 15973, Trichinocrinus terranovicus taken by T.W. Broadhead (Univ. Tenn). 3x4 black and white print. 1987?, 000555
    - Photographs & Negatives. Four 3x4 black and white prints of YPM 18248, Protopliomerops contracta; YPM 18259, Protopliomerops celsaora; YPM 18257, Protopliomerops contracta. Black and white prints, 1987; 000563
    - Photographs & Negatives. Two photographs at different enlargements of IP.322470. Ceratitis (Pterandrus) rosa?, 1989; 002742
    - Photographs & Negatives. trilobite: five 4x6 color prints of YPM 7399, Pliomerops canandensis; YPM 27810, Cornuproetus beecheri; YPM 28256, Triarthrus eatoni legs (2 photo prints); One double X-ray of Triarthrus eatoni YPM 228 (same specimen x-rayed by Cisne); Color print; Black & White print, 1990; 000557
    - Photographs & Negatives. One 5x7 black and white print and one 4x6 negative of YPM 9156, Heliophyllum halli. 5x7 black and white print; 4x5 negative. ca 1990, 000558
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white negatives and black and white prints of Lower Devonian Helderbergian crinoid slab, which is mounted on the second floor of the Peabody Museum. Prints prepared for postilla article by J.K. Hicks and C. Wray. black and white prints/negatives, 1990; 000594
    - Photographs & Negatives. 4x5 negative of complete Lower Devonian Helderbergian, New York, crinoid slab which is mounted on the second floor of the Peabody Museum. Photo taken by W.K. Sacco for exhibit label., 1994; 000482
    - Photographs & Negatives. 4x5 negative of left center of Lower Devonian Helderbergian, New York, crinoid slab which is mounted on the second floor of the Peabody Museum. Photo taken by W.K. Sacco for exhibit label., 1994; 000483
    - Photographs & Negatives. 4x5 negative of lower center portion of Lower Devonian Helderbergian, New York, crinoid slab which is mounted on the second floor of the Peabody Museum, Photo taken by W.K. Sacco for exhibit label, 1994; 000484
    - Photographs & Negatives. 4x5 negative of upper right portion of Lower Devonian Helderbergian, New York, crinoid slab, which is mounted on the second floor of the Peabody Museum. Photo taken by W.K. Sacco for exhibit label, 1994; 000485
    - Photographs & Negatives. Two 8x10 black/white photographs of the Lower Devonian Helderbergian, New York, crinoid slab, Photo taken by W.K. Sacco for exhibit label, 1994; 000486
    - Photographs & Negatives. one 8x10 black/white photograph of the upper right corner of the Lower Devonian Helderbergian, New York, crinoid slab, which is mounted on the second floor of the Peabody Museum. Photo taken by W.K. Sacco for exhibit label. black and white photo, 1994; 000487
    - Photographs & Negatives. 8x10 photograph of the upper left corner of the Lower Devonian Helderbergian crinoid slab, Lower Devonian Helderbergian, New York, which is mounted of the second floor of the Peabody Museum. Photo taken by W.K. Sacco for exhibit label; photo of center left area., 1994; 000488
    - Photographs & Negatives. 8x10 photograph of lower center portion of Lower Devonian Helderbergian, New York, crinoid slab, which is mounted on the second floor of the Peabody Museum. Photo taken by W.K. Sacco for exhibit label., 1994; 000489
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white 4x5 negative and prints of YPM 33160 (Assemblage slab of Mormolucoides articulatus including YPM 27497 and 36245 - 36258 (individual specimens of M. articulatus)) and closeup of YPM 27497. Photos taken at the request of Phil Huber., 1997; 000647
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white 4x5 negative and prints of Mormolucoides articulatus including YPM 36243 (Assemblage slab including YPM 36244), YPM 36241 (Assemblage slab including YPM 36242) and YPM 27499. Prints at 4x., 1997; 000650
    - Photographs & Negatives. bl & wh prints & neg of Ghost larvae Jurrassic of Massachusetts; ypm 36419, 1997; 000658
    - Photographs & Negatives. 3 black & white photos and drawing of Neridavus (029363)., 1997; 000660
    - Photographs & Negatives. Documents, plastic overlay tracing, black & white photos & negatives, & color slides related to orientation study of Uintacrinus heads on slab YPM 024758 (includes YPM 158001-158196), 1998; 000685
    - Photographs & Negatives. YPM 160726, Phytopsis tubulosum, Black & white negatives & 35 mm color slides., 2000; 000732
    - Photographs & Negatives. black & white 35 mm negatives of gastropod bore holes in Cretaceous inoceramid, Cataceramus., 2002; 000757
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black & White contact prints and 5x7 negatives of YPM 5552, Cyathophyllum proliferum Hall; YPM ?, Favosites argus Hall; YPM ?, Roemeraster; YPM ?, Streptelasma corniculum Hall; YPM ?, Homotelus bromidensis; YPM 4126, Halloceras ornatum; YPM 6571, Ceraurus. Black & White contact prints and 5 x 7 negatives, 000544
    - Photographs & Negatives. Two 4x5 black and white prints of YPM 18609, Stylonurus lacranus. 4x5 black and white prints, 000552
    - Photographs & Negatives. One 4x5 black and white print and two 4x5 negatives of YPM 18612, Eurypterus lacustris. 4x5 black and white print & 4x5 negatives, 000553
    - Photographs & Negatives. Three 3x5 black and white prints of YPM 31692, Olenellus getzi. Black and white print, 000559
    - Photographs & Negatives. One color 4x5 negative and one 8x10 color print of the Burgess Shale diorama at the Smithonian Institution (USNM). 4x5 color negative; 8x10 color print, 000566
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints of Aliscrinus tetramartus. YPM 27028-29. black and white prints, 000597
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints of YPM 525, Argobuccium. black and white prints, 000598
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white negatives and prints of Permian fusulines from Western China Black and white negatives and prints, 000600
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white negatives of late Devonian Brachiopods black and white negatives, 000602
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white negatives of Z. Yang's dissertation including bivalves. Black and white negatives, 000607
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white glass negatives of Pennsylvanian Mazon Creek cockroaches, 000632
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white glass negatives of Cephalopoda [nautilloidea], 000633
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white glass negatives of Pennsylvanian Mazon Creek Arachnida [scorpions & spiders]; Peabody Museum specimens, 000634
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white glass negatives of Pennsylvanian Mazon Creek Arachnida [scorpions and spiders]; Peabody Museum colls., 000635
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white glass negatives of Pennsylvanian Mazon Creek Arachnida [scorpions and spiders] - Peabody Museum specimens, 000636
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white glass negatives of Arachnida [scorpions and spiders] of Pennsylvanian Mazon Creek; Daniels coll., 000637
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white glass negatives of Arachnida [scorpions and spiders] of Pennsylvanian Mazon Creek- Chicago collections, 000638
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white glass negatives of Pennsylvanian Mazon Creek Arachnida [scorpions and spiders], USNM colls. (2 boxes), 000639
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white photographs, negatives and prints of Newfoundland fossils from Lieth's unfinished PhD dissertation; in 1 small and one large box, 000643
    - Photographs & Negatives. Master set of Digital Images of invertebrate fossils from the Yale Peabody Museum, Division of Invertebrate Paleontology. Includes portraits (paintings) of Beecher, Schuchert, Dunbar, Waage, 000672
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white photographs of fusulinids from eight localities in Texas. M. E. Upson, Accn. IPA.07544, 002427
    - Photographs. One 3x5 black and white print of YPM 24777, Ichthyocrinus schucherti Black and white print, 1905; 000556
    - Photographs. One 8x10 black and white print of YPM Nos. 8549, 32989, 32999, 33000, 34951 and 34952, a slab of crinoids from Legrand, Iowa. Black and white print. ca 1920, 000565
    - Photographs. Two 6x8 black and white prints of invertebrate fossil displays showing coral and trilobite diversity from the original Sachem St. building; one 7x9 black and white print of the large slab of Uintacrinus socialis (YPM 24758) [before it was broken]. black and white prints. ca 1930, 000548
    - Photographs. Photographs of Diplotrypa schucherti Fritz, YPM 24950., 1966; 000705
    - Photographs. Nine 2x4 black and white prints of brachiopods from Anticosti Island includiung YPM 10341, Clorinda becsciensis; YPM 10357, Virgiana barrandei anticostiensis. Black and white prints, 1996; 000561
    - Photographs. hard copy of one compact disc (CD) containing digital photos of about 50 lots from systematic and type trilobites; taken by T. Whiteley., 2003; 000792
    - Photographs. Digital photographs and prints of pyritized trilobite specimens, 2003; 002424
    - Photographs of Asteriacites lumbricalis and a protasterid ophiuroid taken by Ron West and E. L. Ward. The specimens are with an unknown private collector, but the images were used in a GSA talk by E. L. Ward in 1982 ("A new ophiuroid from the Pennsylvanian of Kansas, associated with the ichnofossil Asteriacites." GSA, South-Central Section, abstracts, 14: 139.) and in a chapter of Art Boucot's 1990 book "Evolutionary paleobiology aof behavior and coevolution" (see IPR.12780)., 1982-2001; 002713
    - Photographs of specimens from Sam Ciurca. Includes a specimen on the same slab as IP.237273, a head and telson of Eurypterus pittsfordensis collected 11-9-13, and a Lingula slab collected 11-9-13. Also includes photos of Ciurca #022904-1A, 022904-1B, 042704-1., 2013-2015; 002714
    - 4x6" photos of George Rennie's models of Anomalocaris, Mixopterus, Ottoia and Terataspis, 000968
    - negatives in sleeves of scaphitid ammonoids, includes images of some embryonic shells, 003212
    - Three compact discs - two containing photographs of the specimens, and the third containing data regarding localities and identifications. All of Green River insect specimens from Jim Barkley., 003223
- Field Notebooks, Series IV
  - 1861-1900., 001285
    - Field notes. 1861 field notes (transcribed by Schuchert) & strat. section, Anticosti Island, Quebec, Canada, 000846
  - 1901-1920., 001286
    - Field notes. Field Notebook: Virginia., 1911; 000253
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Oklahoma., 1905; 000065
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Illinois, Missouri., 1906; 000066
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Illinois, Missouri., 1906; 000222
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Oklahoma., 1907; 000064
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Virginia., 1910; 000254
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Virginia., 1911; 000255
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Virginia., 1911; 000256
  - 1921-1940., 001287
    - Field notes. Field notebooks: New York. 1927; 1928; 1929; 1931, 000438
    - Field notes. Field notebook: Quebec; Gaspe., 1929; 000437
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Newfoundland., 1933; 000058
    - Notebook. Field Notebook, list of Yang [unpubl.] types, and shipping invoices: Indiana, Michigan, New York, Ohio, Ontario, Pennsylvania., 1938; 000157
    - Notebook. Field Notebook and sketch map: Quebec., 1938; 000158
    - Notebook. Field Notebook (#3): Victoria Island, NWT, Canada., 1939; 000159
  - 1941-1960., 001288
    - Field notes. field notebook: South Dakota, Nebraska, Kansas, Colorado., 1942; 000398
    - Field notes. field notebook: South Dakota, Nebraska, Kansas, Colorado., 1944; 000399
    - Field notes. Field notebook #1 (1955); Arizona, Cochise & Pima Counties; Whetstone Mountains; Paleozoic and Cretaceous., 000762
    - Field notes. Field notebook #2 (1955); Arizona, Cochise & Pima Counties; Whetstone Mountains; Paleozoic and Cretaceous., 000763
    - Field notes. Field notebook #1 (1956); Arizona, Cochise & Pima Counties; Whetstone Mountains; Paleozoic and Cretaceous., 000764
    - Field notes. Field notebook #2 (1956); with topo. map; Arizona, Cochise & Pima Counties; Whetstone Mountains; Paleozoic and Cretaceous., 000765
    - Field notes. Field notebook #3 (1956); Arizona, Cochise & Pima Counties; Whetstone Mountains; Paleozoic and Cretaceous., 000766
    - Field notes. Field notebook #1 [or 6]: Texas, New Mexico., 1958; 000535
    - Field notes. Field notebook #2 [or 7]: Texas, New Mexico., 1959; 000536
    - Guidebook. Guidebooks and associated field notes from the following countries. AFRICA: South Africa, Morocco, Mauritania. EUROPE: Turkey, Cyprus, Norway, Spain, France, United Kingdom, Switzerland, Romania, Ireland, Czeckoslovakia, Hungary, Portugal, Austria, Germany, Greece, Sweden, Yugoslavia, Russia, AUSTRALIA. ASIA: Papua, China. CARIBBEAN: Jamaica. CENTRAL AMERICA: Costa Rica, Guatemala. SOUTH AMERICA: Chile. NORTH AMERICA: Canada, Mexico, United States [ ]. ca 1940-1999, 000709
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Idaho, Utah., 1946; 000067
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Idaho, Utah., 1947; 000068
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Idaho, Utah., 1947; 000069
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Idaho, Utah., 1947; 000070
    - Notebook. Field Notebook, photocopy: Missouri., 1953; 000270
    - Notebook. Field Notebook, photocopy: Missouri., 1953; 000271
    - Notebook. Field Notebook, photocopy: Missouri. 1953, 1954, 000272
  - 1961-1980., 001289
    - Field notes. Catalog of field collection: Egypt. 1965, 1966, 000194
    - Field notes. Field notebook for Cretaceous of Saskatchewan, Canada, & Montana, USA, 1965; 000843
    - Field notes. Field notebook for Cretaceous of Montana, 1966; 000844
    - Field notes. Field notebook for Cretaceous of Montana; with photos, 1967; 000845
    - Field notes. field Notebook: Wyoming., 1976; 000433
    - Field notes. field Notebook: Wyoming., 1976; 000434
  - 1981-2000., 001290
    - Field notes. Field notebook: Quebec. 1981, 1982, 000306
    - Field notes. Field notebook: Quebec. 1982, 1983, 000307
    - Field notes. Field notebook: Quebec., 1983; 000308
    - Field notes. notebook for stromatoporoid field trip to Silurian & Devonian of New York, Ohio, Michigan, & Ontario, Canada. & Fagerstrom locs from his 1982 GSC Bull 339., 1983; 000902
    - Field notes. locality information (photocopies of field notebook and map), Montana, Cretaceous Bearpay Sh, 1988; 000882
    - Notebook. Field notebook, sketch map of Alcova Ls locales: Wyoming., 1983; 000300
    - Notebook. Middle Devonian Stromatoporoidea from Southern Ontario (notebook leading to IPR.06952 - Lower Middle Devonian Stromatoporoidea from Empire Beach, Southern Ontario, Canada - St. Jean, 1986, Journal of Paleontology 60(5):1029-1055), 000910
  - 2001- Present., 001291
    - Notebook. Field notes: 13th Field Conference of the Cambrian Stage Subdivision Working Group - The Siberian Platform, Russia, 2008; 000918
  - Undated., 001292
    - Field notes. Devonian, West Virginia and other places, 000802